A Guide to the University of Virginia Archives Authority File, 1924, 1953-2008
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy (VGHPP) 1978 February 1, 1 item (Box-folder 5:25)
  Includes University Register article "VFHPP Takes Humanities to the Public."
- Wahoo 1978-1981, 5 items (Box-folder 5:26)
  Includes news clippings regarding University of Virginia lingo, cheers, and culture.
- Washington Society n.d., 1 item (Box-folder 5:27)
  Includes page from The Colonnades (not related to Washington Society).
- White, William H.: Foundation Lecturers 1923-1937, 1 item (Box-folder 5:28)
  Includes list of lecturers and topics.
- White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs 1972-1986, 7 items (Box-folder 5:29)
  Includes news clippings and list of new and backlist titles from the Miller Center.
- Wilson, Woodrow 1921-1981, 6 items (Box-folder 5:30)
  Includes room occupancy record, correspondence regarding a bronze plaque dedicated to Wilson's old room, and history of University of Virginia information regarding Wilson's attendance.
- World War II 1938-1946, 3 items (Box-folder 5:31)
  Includes Alumni Bulletin regarding WWII memorial, list of University alumni awarded medals during the war, and a list of University alumni casualties of the war.
- Writers-In-Residence 1957-1987, 1 item (Box-folder 5:32)
  Includes list of writers and dates of residence.